Iinari Expedition! Iinari Expedition!
This way! Ichirogu no Starlust!
Iinari to! Kusanachan! Please take good care of me!
I'm Karen Fuchihara!
I'm Yuna Waki!
I'm Karen Fuchihara and I'm Yuna Kazuki!
Today, we have Karen and Yuna!
Today, you can see in the back of this picture...
It's that time of the year again!
I'll make an announcement right away!
Yes!
Let's enjoy the beer garden for today's exploration!
Great! Thanks for having me!
I just want to say one thing. To Yuna, I'd like to say...
What is it?
Yuna, this beer garden project is an annual event.
This is probably the fourth time. This year.
That's great!
It's the only time of year I come here. You Explorers.
Because it's the first time since last year's beer garden video. Maybe you'll appear in it.
What? No way.
No way!
Oh, he's coming!
He's coming to drink, isn't he?
And we've done it four years in a row.
This is my fourth time.
I've been three times out of four.
Beer Garden Video
Seriously...?
That's what he's going for, isn't it?
Wait a minute. What do you mean?
We want to know. What do you mean?
But they said something about a beer garden project.
Afterwards, of course.
I thought you were invited because of the beer garden.
No, no, no.
Well, I didn't come here to drink.
But this is the third time every year.
of this project.
This project's for sure.
So I'm going to introduce it again this year.
And Karen, who's making her first appearance in the beer garden video.
It's her first appearance.
She's here.
I'll tell you about it.
I'd like you two to introduce some of the things you'll be doing today.
Okay.
First of all, I'd like you to take a quick look at the menu.
Take a look at this menu.
Let's take a look.
All you can eat and drink.
90 minutes, 120 minutes.
And there are more kinds of food.
That's great.
All you can eat and drink.
Not only meat every year.
It's not only meat, but also crab, like this one here. Isn't it amazing? Isn't it amazing? Crab on the barbecue?
It goes up! There's more than we can eat.
This is awesome!
I'm going to order the premium plan today.
All of it! Really?
There's nothing I can't eat.
No, you didn't.
Are you sure? Thank you!
I hope you enjoy the food and drink.
I hope you'll tell the viewers how good it is.
I'll do my best.
Well then, let's order and eat!
Yes!
Well, now that we're seated...
I'd like to order.
This year, we decided not to order normally.
What? What?
Until last year, you could order meat and drinks.
Or get a drink or something.
And some other things like that.
But this year, I'm thinking of changing it up a bit.
I thought it was a little bit awkward.
If you want to order something, you have to fulfill a mission from me.
For example, if you want to order meat, this mission, if you want to order crab, this mission, if you want to order a drink, this mission...
If you don't clear it, you can't order anything.
If you don't clear it, you can't eat anything for 120 minutes.
So, it's
It's hard!
Let's do our best!
Let's clear it.
I'll do my best
At first, let's start with a few items
I'd like you to decide what you'd like to eat at least.
I'd like you to decide now.
I see.
It's meat, isn't it?
I want to eat it.
Namegama saru and sanchu.
And something to drink.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
I'll take just one meal there.
I'll take a set with the reverse....
One set is enough to complete the first mission.
It's the first mission.
Are you two going to do this?
One at a time.
One at a time?
It's loose at first.
Here's your first mission.
Excuse me.
Ready?
Come on, let's go!
I'm here to show you what I had for dinner last night.
What did we eat last night?
That's where it starts.
Yesterday?
Oh, I remember now.
Are you waiting?
There are other customers here.
They're on the fourth floor.
You'll have to speak louder.
My dinner last night.
Like this.
I'm so embarrassed.
This is for two people.
I got a set of 3 kinds of samgyeopsal!
But I want to eat it, so let's do it.
You're not going to eat it.
But there are people here.
There are people here.
Babies, too.
Well, I'd like you to try the first mission.
It's no fun to say it right there.
There's a stage on the fourth floor.
So I want you to go up there and yell out what you had for dinner last night.
"I ate dinner last night" at the top of your lungs, one by one.
The camera won't follow us.
I'm shooting from a distance.
Hey, follow me.
This is serious.
What the fuck?
I don't like it.
It's okay. You've been on stage before.
I'm sure there have been plenty of times when you've been a little more nervous than this, but this is the most embarrassing.
Well, Karen, you can start. We'll be watching.
Don't be such a pussy.
Dad, you're clapping.
My dinner last night was...
Jell-O beige pasta.
What applause?
It's rather expensive
It's rather expensive, guys, but
What applause?
He was so angry. He was so angry.
Thank you, guys.
Can I ask you one more time?
I'm going to have Sinobeja pasta with my sister for dinner last night.
We went out to dinner.
Good, good, good.
She died after that.
I can't speak like that.
Can I buy you something that's not dinner?
No, no, no.
Can I use my charm factor?
Charm points are fine.
My charm points are...
Good night.
Charm point is fine.
Charm points?
My charm points are...
Well, you know...
If you have a lot of them, that's fine.
I'll make it a charm point.
You can tell me what you had for dinner.
No, no, no.
Which one is better?
Which is better?
Which one's not funny?
Which one is better?
Let's go to Cab Point.
It's better if everyone knows, right?
I'm sure they'll love it.
I'll go tell them.
Show them off.
Go for it!
Good luck.
I'm watching so much, and I'm lucky to have parents and kids.
They're cracking up.
Hey, what's up, what's up, what's up?
Hey, hey, there's a weird guy up here.
There's a weirdo up on stage.
That's me.
I can't hear you.
I don't know what to do.
My charm point is...
My nose rabbi.
Oh!
LOL!
I just figured out that it's some kind of chanpon.
I don't know, it's just so funny.
The atmosphere is funny.
The kids are clapping.
A grown woman suddenly appears
She's wearing my chanko and flowers.
Okay.
Get it?
I got the subgyeopsal!
It's going to be good.
No, it's good.
It's so warm.
What was that? What else did we have? Drinks.
I'd like a drink.
I want a drink.
Oh, you're so cute.
We're on a mission, aren't we?
What do I shout next?
Aren't you getting used to it? Do it again.
Anything.
Okay, here you go.
I want something a little lighter.
We don't have anything light.
Here we go. Ready?
My favorite fruit.
I'll design it for you.
Yes, sir.
You know what I mean? What do you mean?
I've never done it before.
Do you have two favorite fruits by the way?
Strawberry.
Kiwi
If it is Yuna, I think I am a strawberry.
Think of yourself as a strawberry.
Think you are a strawberry and dance!
Strawberry dance
There's no sound.
There's no sound. There's no sound.
It's rather long.
So when people see it from a distance...
"Oh, Strawberry is dancing...
Strawberry is dancing.
I see.
That's so hard!
Ms. Kawaren is a cucumber
Cucumber
Strawberry dance
Let's do Strawberry Dance!
Strawberry Dance with Yuna Azuki
10 seconds
Long time
Hell, hell, hell
20 seconds
There is still time.
There's still time.
Long time.
Long.
We're done.
It's over.
Oh, my God.
This is the hardest thing I've ever done on an expedition.
I've never done this before.
It's been a while since I've been here, but this is a hard show.
Okay, Karen, go on.
Good luck.
Ninth place, right?
Ninth place is a little hard to come by.
But I think we're a little too close.
I think we're getting a little too close.
Let's look at it from a little farther away.
It looks like we're filming something.
That's right.
Let's look at it from the edge.
I'm going to look at it from a distance.
From a distance.
Don't do it so fast.
Suddenly dance.
Please, please, please.
My neck's jammed.
His neck's jammed.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha.
He's mad.
It hurts inside.
Ha ha ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I'm starting to feel like a person who just does exercises.
Health Exercise
Bathroom exercises, round and round, pakahn
Pakkan
Aaaaah!
That's enough.
I'm looking at it carefully.
I'm sorry, Kane-san.
I forgot to tell you the time.
We're done.
They're here, they're here, they're here.
I didn't call for you.
I'm going home.
It was wonderful.
Oh, my God, I'm going home.
You can eat now.
You can eat!
Now we have three kinds of samgyeopsal and a drink.
Let's go get them.
Let's get our drinks.
What shall we drink?
You're over 20 years old now, right?
That's right.
Let's have something to drink.
What about alcohol?
Sake?
What? That pattern?
We saw this pattern last year with Hikaru-san.
But free... soft drinks are fine.
Yes!
Okay, then...
Oh, so that's how it is.
No strawberry milk or anything like that.
Okay, it's got to be mild.
Oh, well, then...
Yes!
Oh, yeah? You're not much of a drinker, are you?
Most people who react to alcohol drink it.
That's my guess.
I'm surprised I don't drink more than you.
What? Character?
You're a character?
Poor girl.
You're trying so hard.
Hey, don't do that.
Poor girl.
You're trying so hard.
Oh, green tea.
Looks good.
How about you, Yuna?
You don't have to strain yourself.
I'll have ginger ale, too.
It's totally fine.
I'll have some ginger ale.
You're going somewhere else.
Where is it?
Gin and tonic.
I see you've mastered that kind of booze.
I got some samgyeopsal, sunchu and a drink.
Let's eat.
First, Grape Root Sour and Green Tea.
Cheers!
To the sun.
What time is it?
It's 3:00.
We won.
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
Let's throw it in!
In the past beer garden videos, I've heard that you went to a barbecue party with the other members.
I've never heard that story from Karen's point of view.
What is his role when the members go out for Yakiniku? Like Yuna and Rinne are in charge of grilling the meat?
That's what I've heard so far.
Is Karen just going to eat the meat?
Karen tries to do something, but she's always in the wrong place.
She told me I didn't have to do it.
You know what?
I just do.
I said I repeated it earlier.
Oh, yeah.
He tries.
Do you have a favorite part of the meat? Ribs? Harami?
Gatsu.
This is my first time.
Really?
You really do this? I've never heard of it.
No one says "gatsu" first.
I've never heard of it.
Or throat whistle.
Isn't that grilled chicken?
Not yakitori?
It's my favorite meat.
I can't really eat ribs or anything like that.
I eat it, but it's chewy. I enjoy eating it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Wow.
And the joints?
Hmmm...
The knobbly ones?
Oh, I love it.
I love it.
Put the meat on the table like this, please.
Wow, that's great.
And this.
Roll this up.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'll go first.
I'm going to have some of this year's samgyeopsal.
I'll have some of this year's samgyeopsal.
2024 samgyeopsal!
Bon appétit!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Kokon.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Please enjoy Shibayu and Karan's smiles.
Mmm! So delicious!
The fat in the meat is so delicious!
Delicious!
It's going to be okay this year too!
Passed!
Then, Kane-kun, I'd like to try Kasa-san's recommendation
I'd like to try adding sesame oil pepper!
Yes!
Yes! Delicious!
It's so good!
It's good at the end!
Yeah!
But the sauce is delicious!
Everything matches!
It's so good!
The meat has the right amount of fat.
So delicious!
Great, I love samgyeopsal out here!
I want to try the other ones too!
There's a lot to choose from.
Do you want to order more?
I do.
What would you like to eat?
I want dumplings.
Let's order.
Okay, let's go, let's go.
Okay, then.
Let's call it a mission of crab and dumplings, shall we?
This way, please.
I'm scared.
Scary.
I think I'm good at this.
Okay.
Look at the camera in a cute, mocking way, please.
I think I'm good at that.
I want to order spicy dumplings.
Please look at the camera and ask for it in a cute and mocking way.
It's like Mr. Tawork's recent work.
I'm sure you can do it now.
Please do!
I want to eat a bite of dumpling from the neck.
Cute!
So cute!
I think I just said the same line as the viewer.
It was cute.
But I'm more of a professional.
I was a professional.
I'm a character who does cute things.
Character?
Lineage
Professional? It sounds like you do it for a living.
Is that it?
Well, yes.
I'm good at it.
I'm not cut out for it.
I'm not cut out for this.
Let's order crabs.
Kanen, I want to eat crab.
Crab.
No way!
He laughed, didn't he?
I didn't know there was such a thing.
They were laughing, weren't they?
There are things you shouldn't do.
You shouldn't have laughed.
No, you shouldn't.
Crab, then.
Yuna, crab.
Let's try to get crabs!
Please, Yuna, please.
Ah, so cute!
So cute!
I'm cute
Cute.
Crab...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey! Hey!
Mr. Cali, can you please riffle?
Yes, ma'am.
Crab, crab, crab.
Mr. Crabby wants to see you, Karen.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Okay.
I just want to disappear.
Let's eat!
Okay, you got it.
Yay!
We got spicy dumplings and crab!
Oh, my gosh!
It just came!
Looks so delicious!
Gyoza!
Oh, my gosh!
Crab!
Lots of crab!
Spicy bite-sized dumplings
It's really just a bite!
Looks like a good snack!
Yes, indeed!
Do you drink?
Uh, no, I don't know.
This looks good.
Looks good. Looks good.
Bon appétit.
Mmm! Crunchy!
Wow, looks good. Sounds good.
Delicious!
Sorry, I'm really good with spicy food.
I'm too good at spicy food.
Slightly spicy.
Oh, I see.
Spicy too?
I'm good at it.
So even those who don't like spicy food can eat it.
I see.
I'm not that good at it.
I want to try it.
But they're really good as dumplings.
They're really good as dumplings.
Yeah, yeah, they're crispy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not too spicy? There.
It's just right.
This is spicy.
Oh, really? Soda, then.
It's just right.
I see what you mean.
You can definitely eat it in one bite.
This is so good.
Well, let's eat crab while we're at it.
I'm on a mission to order the next one.
One of the talking ones.
For your enjoyment.
So let's eat crab while doing that.
That's what we're doing!
We'll talk to each other about each other.
Karen from Yuna's point of view Karen from Yuna's point of view
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
Bon appétit!
Delicious
The meat is firm.
You can eat meat and fish.
It's great, isn't it?
It's great.
Karen Tachibana.
What do you think? From your point of view.
Yes, I think so.
What will she say?
She'll probably give you a lot of crap.
I'm doing my best.
Why from the top?
You didn't get in too well, did you?
Maybe.
Compared to before.
During the MC.
I often cry before the show.
And during rehearsals.
I often feel like I'm in a lot of pain.
I've seen a lot of situations where I'm about to cry even if I don't cry.
But recently I don't cry so much.
Of course there are many times when I cry during MC
I don't cry as much as I used to.
But I think that's a good thing.
It's not something I'm used to.
It means I'm getting stronger.
I was thinking a little too much about it, wasn't I?
That's what you saw.
Yuno is the deputy leader.
I'm going to be 22 years old.
With age.
I think she's lightened up in a good way.
I see... in a good way.
I think you can relax more.
You can be more relaxed.
You can relax more.
That's right.
I don't mean tears.
I'm saying you can relax to the point of drooling.
That's taking it to the extreme.
You can't really do that.
That's a bit much, isn't it?
I mean, you shouldn't drool, but of course you shouldn't.
It's too loud.
It's just a metaphor, it's just a metaphor.
I see.
That's about the extent of it.
I don't need idols to drool.
So you're saying...
I see.
That's great.
What do you think of that?
What do you think?
Karen thinks it's...
It's so good.
Yes, it is.
I mean, I'm aware of it.
I mean, my personality has changed a lot.
My personality has changed.
Your personality has changed a lot.
Wow.
That's amazing.
Amazing.
In a good way.
Good.
Positive.
I'm a little less negative.
I'm not as negative as I used to be.
I'm more accepting of myself.
I don't accept who I am.
And the overthinking.
I think that's a big part of it.
I see.
I blamed myself for not being able to do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've been telling people to stop telling him about the changes right before the show, but lately, I've been having a hard time understanding it.
I've been asking people to please stop telling him about the changes right before the show, but lately I've been full of it, because I understand.
Yes, I understand.
You understand, and the members around you understand, so it's running well.
That's great.
That's Yuna-chan!
Yuna, you're always looking out for those around you.
That's why you're a catcher.
She's a catcher.
The key to Tork's fan.
Yuna is the only one.
Let's do it the other way around.
Karen to Yuna.
Yuna's.
She's all grown up.
What?
What do you mean?
Her personality, the way she performs...
Personally, I think she's become a very good adult.
Wow!
What was that?
Yuna seems to be able to see more things than other people.
You can think about things.
And she's the type of person who cares about not only herself but also other things, this and that.
I think she is always aware of various things, and she is always hurting.
But I also see him swallow them all by himself.
I often see that they try their best to make up for it.
I guess that's what makes me Yuna-chan.
I wondered if I wouldn't ruin myself by hoarding too much.
But that's all part of it.
I don't know if it's right to say that I'm becoming an adult.
I don't know if it's right to say that I'm becoming an adult, but I do feel that way.
Thank you very much.
It makes me angry.
I'm becoming an adult.
I'm embarrassed.
I see.
So, Karen is also influenced by Yuna, right?
Yes, I have. That's great.
Yuna has a lot of influence, and when Yuna looks happy, everyone looks happy.
You often hear that, don't you? That's right. That's really true.
That's why I'm having fun. If Yuna is having fun at a concert, it's a good concert.
I've heard something about that.
Please don't do that. I have to have fun.
That's not what I meant.
It's just that one more gear is broken.
It breaks.
It's good because it's Yuna or something.
It's just...
Isn't this video too much of an ups and downs?
I was just joking around with you.
How can I listen to such a good story?
It's getting a little too deep.
Let's have a drink.
Okay, we've got one more mission.
We've cleared our bank account.
We can order now.
Pork taffy, plum cucumber and cheese ring.
Understood.
I'm Yuna Asaki.
I'm Karin Tachibana.
The good thing about Toots-san is that they are all interesting.
What I like about Ms. Tootsu is that she has a strong sense of youth.
What I like about Ms. Toots is that she is a good singer.
What I like about Ms. Toots is that she gives her all in everything she does.
Tootsu is a very nice group.
Please come and see us.
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Ume cucumbers.
Cheese ring.
Thank you.
It has arrived!
Then this time, yes.
We need your cooperation.
No, I'm just saving it.
I'm just saving it.
You're just saving it?
Well, you know, just for today.
I'm about intermediate.
The way you hold the tombs, it's very peculiar.
Like chopsticks.
You hold it like chopsticks.
Oh!
Oh...
Like this.
Ah, easy to hold.
It's human evolution.
Thank you.
That's good.
OK.
We've grown.
Good.
Cheeselings, that kind of thing.
You did it.
Cheese ring.
That looks good.
Is it good?
It's so moist and melty.
I love it.
I love that they have snacks too.
I'll have the plum cucumber.
You're so picky.
I've been eating a lot of alcoholic beverages.
Since a while ago.
Mmm.
It's baked quickly.
It's good, right here in the middle.
It's so good.
Looks delicious.
Here's the meat that Karen grilled for us.
I got it.
Are you sure?
Then I'll go ahead and eat first.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Looks delicious!
It tastes even better since Kane-chan grilled it for us.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
It's nice to be told that, isn't it?
I grilled it myself. I raised it myself.
The meat I raised.
Bon appétit!
The meat is so stretchy, isn't it?
Delicious!
I love it when it's crunchy, don't you?
It's so good!
I've never grilled tongue like this before.
It was my first time grilling tongue.
Witnessed a historic moment.
Yes, indeed.
Thank you very much.
It's the anniversary of the first time I grilled tongue.
Then today is
Tang Day.
That's because Allen grilled the tongue.
So today is Tang Day.
I've heard of it.
We had a lot of fun eating today.
Today is the anniversary of the baked tongue.
And now that we've had our feast, it's time for our final mission.
I think we're getting close to Tohoku-san's July solo show in Tokyo.
I'd like you to make an announcement about it.
I'd like you to announce the July one-man show while we're doing this mission.
I see.
Either one of you can be our representative.
Seino.
I'm going to get shot while announcing Tohoku-san's concert.
I see.
Do you understand?
I'll do the air.
Bang!
Like in a cop drama.
Uhh! Like in a cop drama.
But there's one last thing he says.
Like in a cop drama.
He's in pain, but he has one last thing to say.
So I'm going to announce my one-man show in July.
"I want to go at the end.
Please obey my orders.
Ugh!
Karen is good at this kind of thing.
Oh! Nasri's dating.
Don't tell me these things.
Karen is good at this. This kind of thing.
I can't do this kind of thing.
Okay, then.
Yuna is the partner cage you're with.
I understand. I mean, I'm not going to help you.
You know, hold her.
Are you okay?
What the hell are you doing?
I don't know.
All right, let's hear it for Mr. Tork.
Mr. Tork, be careful.
I got your back.
I'm doing something.
I think that's the enemy's hideout.
Almost there. I'll be inside.
I'll be in there.
Stay with me.
Don't die. You're flagging all over the place.
I'll let you go first.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
He won!
Drop your guns!
Who the hell are you? Shoot him!
It's okay! It's okay!
Hazuki, I may not be around much longer.
Just tell them one thing.
What the hell, Tachibana.
On July 26th, Inari Higashi Ward is going to Katsushika Symphony Health.
Zeshonan of the Love Demon Chain!
Next to die
Excitement Danjo
He's talking so much.
Atik yokuhawa ni
Yeah.
Turn around.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I want to make a decision.
Okay, okay.
It's a commentary, introvert.
Is he still talking?
I thought you still had something to say. I have something to say.
There's more, isn't there?
Tell them that the event
That the event is very important.
And also...
Even if I'm not here.
I'll be watching from the sky.
I want you all to have a lifetime of youth.
You have my word.
I promise.
Promise.
Come here.
Oke.
This is a good announcement.
That was a white-knuckle performance, Mr. Kurlen.
It was wonderful.
We've been waiting for you to play Cage.
Yes, well...
Today, we were planning to enjoy the rehearsal garden of Sendai Beads.
Good, the youth deca came back to life.
Thank God, they came back to life!
How was it?
Well, I don't know...
There were some great challenges, but...
But it's so good that you forget everything?
Yes.
I don't know. I thought it was the best!
It's just like this?
This is youth!
Youth!
I really felt like a youth!
It's so nice outside.
I know, right?
Eating the best food and laughing with each other.
That's right.
Everything was delicious.
There's a great atmosphere here.
I love it.
How was Yuno, who does the "good night" video every year?
How was it, Yuno? It was great again this year.
There's no doubt about it. They have a lot of different kinds of food.
Not only yakiniku but also seafood and other snacks.
And you can eat not only grilled meat but also seafood and other snacks as well.
Please try as many as you can!
I hope you all enjoy your meal.
It's going to be open until September 30 this year.
So enjoy your summer!
Please come by after the event.
Have fun!
That's all for today's Iginari Expedition.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
bye-bye!
Seishun
Are you okay, youth?
Youth